Guide to the Douglas Killgore video materials, 1911-2013 UA 405
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Media
  - Scientia #2, (DV), 2012-10-12 (Box 7)
  - Centennial, Shepherd School #1, (DV), 2012-10-14 (Box 7)
  - B'nai Mitzvah of Merissa Leebron and Gregory Robinson, (Beta), 2012-10-20 (Box 7)
  - IMAX #1, (DV), 2012-10-23 (Box 7)
  - IMAX #2, McMurtry, (DV), 2012-10-23 (Box 7)
  - Boniuk #1, (DV), 2012-10-25 (Box 7)
  - Boniuk #2, (DV), 2012-10-25 (Box 7)
  - Fondren #1, (DV), 2012-11-07 (Box 7)
  - Scientia, RMC, Camera 1, #1, (DV), 2012-11-13 (Box 7)
  - Faculty Senate #1, (DV), 2012-11-14 (Box 7)
  - Jason Hafner Physics class (3), (DVD), 2013-01-07 (Box 7)
  - Vision Welcome (2), (DVD), 2013-02-18 (Box 7)
  - Douglas Hofstadter / Analogy as the Core of Cognition, Rice Media, (DVD), undated (Box 7)
  - Rice almost perfect, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Boniuk Audio Music, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - David Leebron: A Bridge Builder Between China and the U.S., (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Susan K. McIntosh: Africa Excavation, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Baker Institute Photos for Rice Fundraising Film, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Pasquali and Hauge ACS (2 DVDs), (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice/Chinese visitors, Houston Rockets LaVergne, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice photos / Jeff Fitlow /Scott Jones, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - "DeBakey Radio Spots" Methodist Hospital, XL Films, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice Smalley DARPA White Paper, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Summer Undergraduate Clinical Research Program, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Kathleen Matthews, Rice Media, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Jill Carroll Interview, Parts 1-3, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice: Leading the New Century Loop Source, Killgore, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Wilcrest Baptist Church, Rice, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Research Images of Lydia Kavraki, Killgore, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Nano Sand Castle Files, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Doug's Backups: .m2ps, Podcast, Bob Curl, Boniuk dinner, Gillis testimonial, RHS Kirby, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Bollywood Dance Red Carpet, Rice EdTech, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Campus Tour and Smalley, Killgore, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - NanoGuin Cake on the Quad, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - COURSERA: Don Johnson intro, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice Architecture?, (film) undated (Box 7)
  - Centennial Symposium, (VHS) undated (Box 7)
  - Smalley, (Beta) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice Nanotube, (VHS) undated (Box 7)
  - Neal Lane, Day 1, (VHS) undated (Box 7)
  - Neal Lane, Day 2, (VHS) undated (Box 7)
  - Science and Technology Policy Conference honoring Neal Lane, tape 3, (DVCAM) undated (Box 7)
  - Science and Technology Policy Conference honoring Neal Lane, tape 2, (DVCAM) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice #3: Freshman week; students coming into Study Hall; exteriors of a few buildings, (DVCAM) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice #7: Segway; Holmes, (DVCAM) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice #12: Cloudman; Smalley, (DVCAM) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice #12: Reckling Field, (DVCAM) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice #11: Ray Strange, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - "Window; Malcolm Lovett", (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - David Parsons #1, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - David Parsons #2, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Jones and Keck Dedication; Bill Barnett Project, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - IT Town Meeting--William Deigaard, Scott Cutler, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Campus bldgs., etc, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Nobelity Opt, Tape 1, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Art Gorski class, shot by Tom, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Art Gorski, Tape 2, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Admissions Video, Nano fundraiser, aerials, Smalley class, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Backpack dub, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Boniuk Lecture Fundamental #1, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Hank Hudspeth, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Rice Dance Remote recording, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Test Canon McMurtry, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Tom in Duncan Hall, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Beer Bike, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - Malcolm Lovett #1, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - FOX-1 + Tudor, (DV) undated (Box 7)
  - GE College Bowl Film (2) scenes of campus, Killgore Productions, (DVD) undated (Box 1)
  - Sandy stills from panel, (DVD) undated (Box 7)
  - Mob Rock: Rice University's "Marching Owl Band", (audio cassette) undated (Box 7)